[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Disclaimer: Characters, locations, and all depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only; viewer discretion is advised]
It's true that I wanted you out back then,
but now, there's nowhere else I want you to be.
I like it...
In a series...
the two male leads have gotta kiss now, right?
Let me ask you, Wan.
Do you like me
or Third more?
You're both fucking assholes.
About #ThirdWan...
Why say sorry about that?
What for?
So you're not maintaining your image anymore?
I'm gonna expose you.
About what?
What do you think...
they're gonna expose about each other?
Did you finish reading all of it?
Huh?
I asked, "Did you finish reading all of it?"
Not yet.
So why are you staring at me?
Nothing.
Keep reading.
Shit, I don't think I'm gonna finish in time.
I need more time to memorize the vocabulary.
Want me to tutor you?
We can make flashcards together.
Thank you, bud.
Anytime.
If I get this scholarship, you've gotta fly to see me.
Do you know my biggest dream
isn't just getting this scholarship?
So what is it?
You're gonna wanna sit down for this, brother.
Damn you! Just spit it out.
Come here. Closer.
I'll tell you.
I wanna be an actor!
Huh?!
But why?
Well, I'll get to shine so bright.
Wherever I go, people will swarm around me, screaming
and taking photos.
"Argh, Nine, Nine, Nine, Nine!"
Damn... Just thinking about it feels like a dream.
What else could I possibly be with this look?
So, with the way I look...
do you think
I'm cute?
Yeah,
you're...
pretty cute.
There!
You're my first ever boy.
What boy?
My fanboy, of course!
Why? Do you wanna be my screen partner?
Shit, but...
Damn it, if we act together,
I'm gonna laugh at your face like I am now.
We just have to look at each other to laugh.
Do you think we can act together?
You're getting ahead of yourself.
Keep reading.
Hey, but...
Here, I'll just go ahead and tutor you.
Sheesh...
Professor Third, by the way.
Here it is, right here.
♫I'm just a fanboy♫
♫I wanna let the world know, you wanna close it♫
♫Just wanna tell you, I'm doing fine, fine♫
♫You won't reveal it, but I won't conceal it♫
♫Trust me, it's alright♫
♫You do you♫
♫You can love whoever♫
♫But I like you forever♫
♫I'm just a fanboy♫
♫No pressure, no drama♫
♫Hakuna Matata♫
♫Just somebody who likes ya♫
♫I'm just a fanboy♫
♫No pressure, no drama♫
♫Hakuna Matata♫
♫Just somebody who likes ya♫
♫I'm just a fanboy♫
[Mr. Fanboy Series]
[Episode 6: "War"]
Wait outside for now. I'll call on you.
You said you wanted Wan to become famous?
Hey...
It's nothing.
A reporter asked, so I answered.
You said, "It's nothing," again.
You do know
I became a producer for this series
because I wanted you to play the lead, right?
Yes.
That's what I used to believe.
And I used to think you'd never let me down again.
Nine...
I wasn't the main one in the last series yet,
and that's fine.
There was nothing I could do since I wasn't the lead.
But I'm already the lead in this one.
It's different now.
You know how long I've been waiting for this.
Wow...
So many fans came to see you today.
Are you tired?
A bit, Mama.
Here, take a seat.
There. I'll get you some water.
Thank you.
Why do you always make a scene?
You think you're the main lead?
Hm?
Talking longer than the main leads...
it's cringe.
It's like you're trying too hard.
If you wanna cause a scene, wait till you're famous, will you?
If you can even be famous, that is.
Hey.
You think you can say anything just because you're famous?
Well, I already said it.
Can I?
If people find out
that the sweet Juno
talks to a coworker like this,
what would they say?
What a cliche threat.
Have you really thought through
who'd actually believe what an extra says?
So why are you afraid of an extra stealing your thunder?
Okay.
From now on, I won't talk too much.
Happy?
Mm...
You catch on fast.
I'd say you're not stupid.
Right...
Congrats on gaining more fans.
I guess people enjoy seeing something fresh.
But don't think you'll be a star just because of those loud squeals,
because in this industry,
skills matter, too.
Hey,
do you hate me, Juno?
Mm.
If you're not happy with that, resign from the project.
Someone like you
probably comes a dime a dozen out there.
Angry?
Good. I like that.
Come on, Aof.
Let's head back.
Hey... Mama.
Move.
Whoa, Mama!
I won't say that again.
Sorry, babe.
"Who do you think you are?
Not answering?
You think I can't do anything to you?
Truth is truth.
No matter what you're hiding,
everyone will find out one day."
Cut!
That's good, Wan.
I totally bought that.
That's very interesting, Wan.
What did you do?
I read the script.
Really?
What?
I'm just asking, yeah?
Because...
it's channeling...
"realistic."
That means your acting was convincing.
Oh...
Oh... that's right.
I forgot I have to translate it.
Okay, take a break.
I like it.
Feel free to go and relax.
"I like it" means...
- he likes... - I think he understands that part.
Right, right.
Thank you.
Of course.
Okay...
I want...
both of you to try
picking up some techniques from their performance.
This is about the scale of it.
Hey, thank you.
Hm?
Luang seems to be satisfied with my acting.
I didn't do anything.
It was all your hard work.
Just let me thank you. It's no big deal.
Guys, I brought you some drinks.
Here you go.
Here's your drink.
Hey, you're getting the gist of the game.
Good on you.
Here's your drink, Nine.
I'm taking a quick restroom break.
Take your time.
In today's class, we'll dig deep into,
or look into,
the characters' desires.
This exercise is called
"Animal Exercise."
Animal!
Think of an animal...
that your character embodies.
Alright, find your own place to lie down.
Relax.
Feel the sensation
as your body presses against the floor.
Slowly transform your body
until you eventually become that animal.
Three...
Two...
Close your eyes, close them.
And one.
And after that,
slowly open your eyes.
Feel that sensation in your body.
Now, feel the energy
and the urge to make a sound.
Be honest,
and make the sound of the animal you are.
That's good, Nine. Amazing. I'm getting goosebumps.
Nice.
Very good, Renji.
Very good.
Charge at another animal
with your energy, your voice,
and your body.
Good...
I'll throw this piece of meat.
It's your last meal.
Whoever gets it
survives.
Nice, nice.
Trust me when I say, on the first day of filming,
I'm refusing to succumb to any B-words out there!
Any B-words who dare compete, bring it on.
You'll catch me fighting from hairline to nape.
Fabulous!
Yes, he's the antagonist, and?
He's crashing 'em with his chest.
To hell with them!
Let me take a look at your face.
Dolly eyes, check.
Contouring, check.
Highlighting, check.
Fabulous!
- Spot on. - With this,
you're piercing through the camera,
out through the TV,
and landing right in your fan's face!
Yes,
because...
Mama didn't raise a loser!
Those crinkly, sky-loft HMUAs,
watch out,
'cause I'll curse them out of the building!
Fabulous!
Right,
seriously though,
why hold such an insane grudge against those sky-loft HMUAs?
Tyrannical.
Lowballers.
They treated us like a fucking doormat.
Am I supposed to repay them with flowers?
Only one kind of flower will do the job.
- Stink bell! - Stink bell!
Right on!
Did that blast your ears?
Natural-looking skin is a must.
I'll give you a nice cut crease.
Today, Mama's male lead will blow 'em away like...
"Pow! Pow! Pow!"
So cinematic, you go, "Bam, bam, bam!"
From every single angle, okay?
Yeah...
Your energy is killing it today.
Abso-freaking-lutely, Mama!
I'm giving it my all
to show those minions
who's boss in this battle.
True that.
Those brush-and-hairdryer newbies,
yuck!
If that were me, I wouldn't hire them, either.
Disgusting!
I feel bad for Renji and Wan, though.
With some shabby MUA
doing a sloppy job,
they're not gonna look as sharp
as you two.
Uh...
Susan,
- so... - What's up?
I've heard something,
but I don't know if it's true.
What is it? Spill.
I heard that Wan...
said some bad things about Third.
Like, really damaging things.
Whoa...
He said that Third was...
a lot to handle
and egotistical.
Brutal!
Yes, it's brutal, but...
I think I should find a way to talk it out with him first.
Ugh...
no need to put this on your plate.
When the timing is perfect,
I'll handle it myself,
okay?
Backhanded positivity?
Am I done?
Oh... you are.
I'll be back, then.
Where are you going?
I'm annoyed.
I'm not in the next scene,
so I'll go get some air.
Alrighty, Wan. Come stand on your mark.
Stand right on your mark.
Okay, Wan is here!
Karn, check the lighting.
Don't you think the villain is wearing too much makeup?
He's trying to steal the show for sure.
Let's tone down his makeup.
Jern.
Gotta run something by you.
Yes, what's up?
Should we tone down Wan's makeup a bit?
I think he has it on so heavy.
Look,
Nine has such a natural look.
Pai, Pai.
What?
Wanna tone down Wan's makeup a bit?
She asked.
Good idea.
It's a little... too heavy.
Okay, okay, okay, alright.
Susan,
give that boy a hand.
Okay, Mama.
Let's go.
That look's hard to work with.
What are these dolly eyes?
Wanna smash everyone while you steal their thunder?
Next time, try...
less gossiping.
You might be easier to work with.
Just a small tip.
Queen,
you're pretty fucking nosy.
This is my job.
Next time, do a good job on the main leads
so you can skip toning down others' makeup.
Right!
Or maybe a crinkly, old MUA like you
just can't keep up with the trends?
Old?
Your mom is!
What kind of makeup is that?
I thought that was a frog-hunting headlamp.
I've never taught you
to do dolly eyes like this.
How about you come back and work for me, carrying my bags?
Doesn't that seem more like your forte?
Jern, are they done?
I'm not going back so you guys
can take your inferiority out on us.
You tyrannical bunch!
Jern...
We once hired you two,
so you must do what we say.
Don't bite the hands that fed you,
ungrateful bitches!
Jern, Jern.
Jern...
Jern!
Jern!!
Are we all good?
We are.
His makeup is good now?
He's nice and toned down.
Okay, if we're all set,
please go back to your spot.
Nine, Nine, come on.
Go to your mark.
Okay...
Here it is, your mark.
Okay, you remember your lines?
I do.
Okay, done with the blocking.
We're good?
Alright, come on.
Right, we're ready to roll.
Crew, quiet!
Ready? Let's go. Roll camera!
Camera rolling!
Set!
- Alright, set! - Set!
And...
Action!
You're just an incompetent guy
who dreams of making it to the top.
Why do you have to be so harsh?
Isn't it true?
I'm just working hard on my part.
Working hard?
Are you working hard,
or sleeping your way to the top?
Sky...
"Truth never dies."
But someone might just die...
if "the truth" gets told.
Cut!
We're through.
Alright, move on to the next scene.
Take Wan to change his hair and makeup.
What the heck are you doing?!
You were good.
Huh?
You did amazing today.
Are you seriously complimenting me?
Why?
Do you prefer I cuss you out?
You're getting on my nerves.
We're both done with our schedules today.
Wanna head out with me?
Are you nuts?
As if Cher would let me.
Don't you wanna go home early?
Just don't forget to tell Cher.
Then, what do I even tell her?
You've got it...
Shoot your shot.
Hey, you.
Is it a good idea to sit out here?
I don't think it is.
No one's around here this late.
But what if someone recognizes you?
You're famous!
It's fine.
I've been here plenty of times.
Hey there, handsome.
Back here again?
So now we're shooing customers?
My, my...
I see you brought someone with you today.
What would you like to order?
What do you wanna eat?
Wonton noodle soup with roasted red pork, please.
- Wonton noodle soup, roasted red pork? - Yes.
And the usual for you, Third?
No chilli flakes, not spicy,
with tons of veggies.
Alrighty.
Give me a moment.
I'll be right back with it.
This is my No. 1 noodle stall,
the best in the entire world.
You like noodles?
Mm.
Mm...
Good.
Then, some other time,
I'll take you to a place that's the best in the galaxy!
Thank you.
Enjoy your food.
Blow on it first.
Alright, Uncle.
Aren't you gonna season it?
Want me to do it for you?
Mm, go ahead.
Let's start with this.
Okay.
Sugar...
Alright,
there you go,
noodle soup for babies.
I guarantee you,
it's delicious.
What do you think?
Be nice.
Don't forget I have hot soup at hand!
How ruthless.
It's delicious, Chef.
No doubt!
Wan,
do you think... I should get hair extensions?
Third might just like me!
Mm, go ahead and get one.
Can you give me money?
No way.
You have your own savings.
Please, can you?!
No!
Not my head, not my problem.
Maybe having long hair isn't even his type.
Fucking cheap...
Oh?
But why are you still here?
Not going on set?
My ride will be here at 5 P.M.
Night calls for night shoots.
Night who?
What's their role?
That's not it...
Here's the thing...
Nighttime scenes
are filmed during night shoots,
so they gather
all the nighttime scenes
for night shoots.
Oh...
since series aren't filmed in chronological order.
Mm.
They group the locations into these shoots.
Right, I was gonna compliment you.
You created some nice buzz from the ceremony.
What? Why the face?
Something happened, huh?
I think...
Nine doesn't like me.
Why would you think so?
Nine entered the dressing room, not knowing I was there.
But do we want Wan to become famous?
- We do, right? - Exactly.
Well... that'd be great.
Scared Wan's gonna become more famous?
How fucking annoying. What do you want?
Be careful, or people will see your true nature.
And Third was saying that...
he'd expose him over something.
Shit...
How are they even partners?
But I wanna know
why they're fighting.
Maybe...
they were boyfriends before?
Huh?!
Why so surprised?!
Dude, it's possible,
giving their over-the-top chemistry.
I don't think...
that's the case?
They're just friends.
That's all the more reason to speculate.
Think about it.
Friends who hate each other this much
must have loved each other deeply once.
And what do Ayutthaya people call former friends
who loathe each other?
Exes!
It feels to me like they were once a real couple.
Trust me.
Hey...
wire me 7,000 baht.
Consulting fee.
I'm getting hair extensions.
Don't forget to wire me.
Wan.
Come with me.
Nine wants to have a word with you.
He said he wanted to talk things out.
Alright...
Nine is up there.
Go have a word up there, just you two,
so no one else can hear.
And talk it out nicely.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Thank you.
Run along.
Go.
You do know
exactly what you're doing, right?
I don't.
Good.
Then, how about we start with you...
chasing clout by jumping off the stage
to help that fan?
She was passing out.
I needed to help her
or no one would.
Then swear
you didn't do it just to compete with me for buzz.
And what does that have to do with anything, Nine?
You're pushing my buttons, you know that?
Then what about the Peppermint Field gig?
You poached that from me.
Do you know a client has called to cancel?
And do you know
who landed the gig?
Wan.
The Peppermint Field gig?
What about it, Nine?
You're fucking unbelievable.
Your acting has gotten so much better, Wan.
Is it because you got your own private coach?
Come on...
Blow the flower on my finger, yeah?
Do you really think he only did this to you?
Huh?
What the hell do you want from me?
Everyone knows you're stealing my partner.
Still confused now?
Oh...
Now you're silent?
Answer me, Wan.
Hey, Nine.
You've got me so wrong.
[On second thought, I think Wan is a better fit for Noel than Nine. Look at the chemistry. #ThirdWan]
And what does this mean?
Come on, explain.
Third asked me to go home together.
We finished our schedules at the same time, so we did.
And?
We just stopped for food.
That's it. Nothing else, Nine.
Are you sure
there's nothing else?
Say it!
If I do,
you're gonna say I'm making excuses.
So that means you know
exactly what you're doing, huh?!
That day,
I let it slide
when you and Third were about to kiss,
and now you think you can do whatever you want?
Huh?
You're into Third!
Admit it.
Fucking admit it, Wan!
I don't have feelings for him!
Bullshit!
Is that by nature,
or something your parents nurtured in you?!
Whoa, Nine!
Why?
Gonna punch me?
Go on!
Punch me.
Do it.
What about you?
Do you admit that you tried to drown me on purpose?
Yeah, I admit it.
Why would you do it?
Why do you hate me so much?!
I'm your fan!
Still have the nerve to call yourself my "fan"?
If I weren't your fan,
why'd I trend your hashtags and mass-stream for you?!
I don't get paid a dime for it!
Did I ask you to?
How the fuck could you say that?!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wan, Wan, Wan, Wan.
I'm sorry.
Wan... I didn't mean to.
Is that it?
Is that what you want?
Huh?
Is that what you imagine in your little head?
That's what you want me to say?!
Huh?!
No.
From now on, I'm not your fan anymore!
Do whatever you want.
Why the fuck are you telling me?!
You know?
I've been wanting to say this shit
to shitty fans like you for ages!
There's one more thing
I'm dying for you to quit doing.
Stop taking my photos and posting them on your account for clout!
Your account...
What the fuck was it?
"onetonine," was it?
Huh?
The photos you took weren't even fucking nice!
When that day arrives, and we come across each other again...
please...
take some nice photos of me.
The engagement, the followers,
and everything else on that fucking account
are all from me!
Not you!
You're just lucky enough to take my photos!
Rest assured.
I'll do everything I can
to help you succeed, Nine,
because I'm your fanboy.
Stop liking me, you fucking bastard!
Fine!
From now on,
I'm done being everything for you.
I'm going to be your rival.
I'll be even better than you.
I'll step on your head.
Wan...
Good job, Wan!
Now, you and I
are speaking the same language, you know that?
But I'll let you in on a secret.
If you want to compete with me,
good luck crawling your way to where I am.
Alright.
Watch your back, though.
Falling from where you are might not hurt,
but it sure is embarrassing.
How?
How so, Wan?
Whoa...
Nine, we're not doing this!
We're not, Wan?
We're not!
But how?
Whoa, Wan?
We're not doing this...
You mean, this?
Whoa, fuck!
Guys, someone fell into the pool!
Help him!
- Go! - Whoa!
Nine!
Nine.
Nine...
Wan,
how could you do this to my baby?!
Huh?!
Whoa!
Oh, goodness!
What the hell are you doing?!
Move!
If you don't,
I'll slap you to the ground!
If you're gonna hurt my baby,
just go ahead and slap me!
Fine.
I'm gonna mess you up!
- Want me to slap the shit out of you, huh?! - Ms. Sunny!
- Ms. Sunny! Miss! - Don't!
- Let go! - Come on, do your worst!
Come at us, I dare you!
If you do, I'll fucking punch you!
You bitch, picking on a woman!
You trashy, nancy pants!
Can you fucking stop?!
Well, these...
- These bitches just... - I said stop!
Why do you keep fucking fighting?!
Well, look at them!
How many times have I said "stop"?!
Look at what they're doing!
Stop!!
Get a fucking grip
and stop being a fucking psycho!
Get what fucking grip?!
Your boy shoved mine into the pool!
Where's the proof?!
Did you see my boy do it with your own eyes?!
Without proof,
this is an accusation.
Renji,
take Wan to pack up, then wait for me at the car.
- Go. - Rin, are you alright?
Where are you running off to?
- Huh?! - Sunny!
- Where are you going?! - Here we go again!
- Come back here! - Pai, go deal with them!
You want a taste of my hand so much?!
- Come here! - Bring it on!
Bring it on!
- How about we stop... - Ugh! Sticking to me like a tick.
- Get them to stop! - Hey!
Ow...
Uh, how about we stop?!
Piss off!
You piss off!
Ugh, stop at once!
Take Nine to the doctor!
Fuck this headscarf!
Listen to me!
Don't breathe a word about what happened on set!
If this gets leaked,
be damn ready to pay up!
I'll
fucking
sue!
Are you okay?
I am, Mama.
Trust me, go to the hospital.
Your hands are freezing cold.
- Huh? - It's fine, it's fine.
I don't wanna blow things out of proportion.
Let's just go...
Nine?
What?
Are you alright?
What happened?
Tell me.
I...
talked to Wan about Third,
and we got into a little fight.
And he pushed you?
Yes.
Okay...
I guess I have to remove him now.
Well... it's all up to you.
Dude, dude, dude,
I just got hair extensions. Isn't it pretty?
Wan?
Do whatever you want.
Why the fuck are you telling me?!
You know?
I've been wanting to say this shit
to shitty fans like you for ages!
Stop taking my photos and posting them on your account for clout!
Hello,
this is Nine.
I hope you have a good day.
I want you all to smile a ton
and be happy every day,
my fans.
Ready to tell me what happened?
He spewed insults at me...
He genuinely hates me.
He said that I post
his photos for my own clout.
Fuck...
Damn it...
This hurts like hell.
It's gonna be fine.
If Nine does anything to you again,
I'm going to the set with you.
I'd better grab a bite.
I'm not gonna die because of this!
That's right!
To hell with them,
but not my brother!
Go find something to eat.
I'll clean this up.
You're getting a piece of me!
I'll clean it up nice and neat!
Whoa...
Why are you here?
To see you, of course.
Are you a sasaeng?
Huh?
You're using that word now?
Right, I forgot...
you're a star now.
Did you come here just to see me?
Mm.
What if I never came down?
I'd go up to your room.
Do you know where my room is?
No.
So why did you come?
I'm worried about you.
Seeing you here,
I don't know how to act.
You don't?
Have you been crying?
Mm...
Come on, let's sneak out!
Huh?
If someone sees us, there'll be another problem.
It's already a big enough deal as it is.
What did you say then?
"The worst that can happen is getting chewed out, no?"
Let's go.
Chop-chop.
Just in case the wind blows the bad feelings away.
I retouched your damn photos!
I slimmed your face down!
I removed those blemishes
and smoothed your skin until my eyes were about to bleed!
I even trended your hashtags until I couldn't move my fingers...
I did everything for you!
But you cussed me out!
I'm done!
I'm fucking done, asshole!
Why is there a bench here?
I brought it from home.
Funny.
Do I look like I'm being funny?
You are...
When I first entered the industry,
I loved coming here.
I liked gazing at the clear, open sky.
It cleared my head.
In this industry,
things can be pretty hard on you,
so I felt like I needed a getaway.
Don't take everything in this world to heart.
It's heavy...
Is it heavy?
Mm...
I never thought
that...
there would be so many things to stress over as an actor.
I thought it was an easy job.
Just dressing up nice,
getting your makeup done,
meeting your fans,
then going home to your family with money.
But in reality,
it's nothing like that.
It's true that being an actor pays well,
but it comes at the cost of carrying so much.
There are plenty of bad things,
but good things come out of it, too.
You just have to find them.
Mm... that's true.
Some good things did happen.
Can you let me in
on those things?
Hm...
I paid off my family's debt.
I still remember the moment I wired Mom that money.
Whoa...
Still new to the industry and already paid it off?
Talk about being fortunate.
What do you mean, "fortunate"?
In return, if I break the contract,
I'll be fined 2 million baht.
That's why I've been grinding nonstop.
So that means there's a reason for you to keep going?
Those who don't love you
have already shown themselves.
How about focusing on those who love you for a change?
Those who love me?
Your fans, that is.
Not to mention Cher.
Mm...
you're right.
I found myself in the same situation you're in.
Some I overcame.
Some I didn't.
What you're facing...
isn't because the industry is bad,
but because of the people.
Not everyone, though.
Not all of them.
Real talk,
how about you try talking like this
when you give interviews to the press?
I bet tons of people will fall in love with you.
You included?
What happened today...
even if everyone on set said you did it,
I wouldn't believe them.
You're...
not gonna hear my side of the story?
I trust you.
I know you'd never do something like that.
What did Nine do to you?
He said I stole his gigs
and...
stole you from him.
One thing I can assure you of
is that you never stole me from him.
I came to you myself.
Thank you...
for saving me.
Instead of a thank-you,
can I ask you not to cry?
Please stop idolizing him.
I'm begging you...
I like you.
Huh?
What was that?
Damn it...
What the actual heck is going on?!
Are you saying you don't like me?
No!
Right...
What even was that "right"?
Uh...
That's not right...
Not right?
So I'm not right for you?
Get your aim right.
♫I'll kiss until you know my love is for you♫
♫And tonight it will be just us two♫
♫Take it as a promise♫
♫Under the stars, I'll give you my kiss♫
♫It is only for you, this kiss♫
♫And I'll hug you so tight♫
♫No matter what tomorrow will be like ♫
♫This promised kiss will keep you alright♫
♫Let my kiss keep you safe and sound♫
♫I'll kiss until you know I'll always be here♫
♫Let my kiss tonight hold you near♫
Babe,
I'm back.
What took you so long?
Aw...
The van had to drop Wan off first.
Ow...
Babe, do you think...
people know
that we're boyfriends?
Wow...
We've almost given it away so many times.
You never play it cool.
Gosh...
Look at how cute my babe is.
Who'd be able to?
And if people find out,
they're gonna squeal like crazy!
Today was fun, wasn't it?
It was.
Though...
I don't understand.
Why did Wan shove Nine into the water?
What nonsense.
I've got something to show you.
Hm?
♫I'm just a fanboy♫
Next one is gonna be fun.
What the hell is this?
This is a fucking rollercoaster.
Tell me the truth.
Whether you did it or not, I'll still help.
I will drive 'Our House' out of the industry entirely.
We have to look for any proof there is.
It's a filming set.
Someone's gotta have seen something.
I'll do whatever it takes
to bring you down to fucking nothing.
Is it because you're worried about yourself?!
Yeah!
Just like you!
I know you might not be happy with this.
How about you go warn Nine?
Why is it always me?!
Let me stay like this for a while.
♫To reach the summit, the more I climb, the colder♫
♫The closer I get to seizing it, the lonelier♫
♫Just like a star so bright,♫
♫The further from the dark nights,♫
♫The more ablaze, primed to burn down♫
♫Just like how I lost touch with people along the way,♫
♫The more steps I took, the more desolate I became♫
♫As though I'm cursed in my soul♫
♫So deeply, I wound everyone who makes me whole♫
♫No one's heart♫
♫Do I want to tear apart♫
♫By my own hands♫
♫But I'm ready to leave it all behind♫
♫Just so I could trade it for the sky♫
♫Even though it pains,♫
♫Even though the trace of tears remains,♫
♫No pain, no gain, no pain, no gain♫
♫Even though it's a long way to the end♫
♫I'm ready to leave it all behind♫
♫Just so I could claim the sky♫
♫I'd sacrifice my being♫
♫Without looking back and regretting♫
♫No pain, no gain, no pain, no gain♫
♫For the end I yearn for in my veins♫
♫I'm hell-bent on moving heaven and earth♫
♫Woah, wo, wo, wo, woah, wo♫
[Mr. Fanboy Series]